[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Did you have a 13-year affair with this woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "Did you know her for 13 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Did you have a 13-year affair with this woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Did you know her for 13 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Wolf, an extraordinary twist today because you weren't expecting him to come out with that until halfway through your interview, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Was this an affair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "No, it was not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "There was no sex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "None?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lynn Wood"], "LOCATION": ["Atlanta"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "What do you make of all this, Wolf?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "It was very strange because Lynn Wood who is a prominent lawyer in Atlanta, he's well known to a lot of TV viewers out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wolf"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "The question is, I guess, can she prove it was inappropriate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Because if it turns out that he is lying about this affair, you would have to imagine that would be the end of his campaign, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Well, you know, you remember the Anthony Weiner case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "What do you make of today's new revelations involving Herman Cain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Well, Piers, certainly if these allegations by Miss White are true, then it certainly goes to the issue of the character and the honesty of Herman Cain.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "I mean, is it really credible that a woman would make a charge of a 13-year affair if there was simply no truth at all to it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Now apparently she has quite a bit of corroboration in the form of at least numerous texts, perhaps e-mails, perhaps other evidence from Herman Cain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Zuckerman"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "In light of what's come out today, Gloria, are you planning any further action with your client?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Not with my client, but I do feel that she is extremely credible and her corroborating witness, one of them, Dr. Zuckerman, the pediatrician, came forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Is this new or does it just seem new?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "It seems new.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Who do you think right now Barack Obama would least want to face?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I think, frankly, that Obama's biggest opponent is the economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Is he terminally shot below the bows now, do you think, in terms of this ongoing series of scandals about his private life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "You'd think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Why does he not get more attention?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I think most people don't know who he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "I like the Big Shaqtus, but which one of those do you particularly like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WDT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "The new name that you just gave me.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Big Shaqtus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "Which one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "The big duke.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "I know it wasn't probably the perfect scripted ending, but do you feel inside you it's the time to go on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "It felt right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Taking up golf yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "'NEAL: No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "With 10 percent of people in this country unemployed, I was like, what are they up to, these guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, you used the wrong choice of words.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What do you think of Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "You know he's the president, and you know, I come from a military background.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Do you think that having the first African- American president has made America more or less racist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I would say less.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "When you've worked your way up from nothing to be what you are, what has happened to stop that kind of thing happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I'm not sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "How to expand beyond the sport?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "But it's pretty awful, isn't it, what's been going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "It's very awful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "I mean, unless I'm mistaken, it wasn't that you hated him, you just both wanted to be top dog, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "And I'm glad you understood that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jordan"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Who is the best player you've ever seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I'll have to go with Michael Jordan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "'NEAL: He knows -- yes, that man right there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "What I've always wondered about you is, do you ever go out and people pick a fight with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "More to do with the fact that you're seven foot tall and could pummel them to pieces?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, maybe a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "When you look back on it, with the exception of the births of your kids and marriage and so on, what is being the one moment you would relive again, that's been the greatest moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "All of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "It's getting better, my accent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "It is getting better.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "How do you feel about still being around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Well, first of all, I've been blessed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "In terms of the medication you had to take every day and so -- how do you keep as healthy as you clearly appear to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Well, first of all, you take the drugs twice a day, but I work out every day, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "It's the World AIDS Day on December 1st, what is the overriding message you would like to communicate on this particular anniversary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I think to continue to help people understand this disease hasn't gone anywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["December 1st"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Shaq", "Shaq"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Do you wish you'd carried on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Well, first of all, you know, dealing with Shaq, Shaq is so amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Or were you more disappointed by those you thought would who didn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Well, I think that I was more shocked that the people who did support me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "That must have really annoyed you, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I'm still mad today about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And if you're playing in a team, a small team of people, and you're both touted by different sets of fans to be number one in the game, there's going to be a rivalry, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "No question about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jordan"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", ",", "CC", ":", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Who's the best you've ever seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Well, Michael Jordan was the best, and -- hands down.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "I would imagine that you walk out and you got Shaq O'Neal bearing down on you, there can't be many worse moments in sports, are there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Well, he's the one I would love to play with.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Shaq O'Neal"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Did it ever happen at al in the current climate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Well, I think when we look back at it, we wish it didn't happen from both the owners side and the players side.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1987"]}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "What is the one basket you scored that if I could give you a minute of your life back, you'd do it again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "1987, the hook shot versus the Celtics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "How often do you think about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "All the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111128pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Every day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Not every day, but all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]